Contact

brudemarco@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bruna-vignolade-marco-92529a23 (LinkedIn) portfoliobruna.netlify.app/ (Portfolio) github.com/brudemarco (Other)

Top Skills

Music Production Music Industry Studio Recording

Certifications

Degree in Advertising

Bruna Vignola de Marco

Nuevas Tecnologías

Argentina

Summary

Hello! My name is Bruna Vignola de Marco and this is my freelance work page:

Here you will see a sample of all the amazing places and work experiences that lead me to search for Frontend projects and study New Technologies.

I have been through a lot of great career experiences since 2013 when I graduated from SAE Barcelona in Audio Engineering, since then I was presented with great opportunities to work with audio, mixing for tv, cinema, and I was also able to participate in amazing recordings for the music business and theater.

The technical environment influenced me to develop an interest in hardware and for that reason, I studied 3D printing in Centro Metropolitano de Diseño Buenos Aires and also built radio transmitters with DTL! Taller de Comunicación Popular - IMPA La Fabrica, there I also learned to solder and work with electronic components, such as simple radio circuit boards or more complicated ones like Raspberry Pi or Arduino. Those last two were the reason I started, not so long ago, to learn how to to program on my own, and now I have online certification by Google in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript (Vanilla).

My first job related to software accessibility and Frontend development was at the beginning of 2020 working for eA essential Accessibility as a Tester and Accessibility QA, after that I had been actively searching for new projects to collaborate in, and also doing freelance work for clients as Centro Cultural España Cordoba, building a website that consists in an accessibility forum diversity inclined: Torceduras y Bifurcaciones.

My goal is to learn and apply new programming languages especially JS this year and also add mobile dev to my deck, in the near future, I have the intention to incorporate more of hardware research technology to my experiences.

Please stick around my page to learn more about my previous experiences and work!

Experience

freelance
Freelance
2020 - Present (less than a year)
Cordoba, Argentina

Front end development and Audio engineering (2013 - Current date)

I started doing freelance work in 2013 when I recorded and produced the album "Ema" in São Paulo, Brasil, and after that, I collected many great experiences in sound editing and also video editing for over 50 clients, also expanding myself into the branch of translating for audio recordings in the tourism industry in 2016.

After 2017 I have also incorporated Front end development into my work and started working and learning for myself and others. I am currently developing a project for the "Foro de corporalidades políticas: Torceduras y Bifurcaciones" a forum that has the objective of being inclusive both in diversity and accessibility. for more information go to www.torcedurasybifurcaciones.com.ar

eSSENTIAL Accessibility Information Technology Trainee January 2020 - June 2020 (6 months) Córdoba Province, Argentina

In this company from Canada, I was part of a great team that was responsible for testing webpages and making sure they were compliant with accessibility requirements, especially based on the wcag 2.1 specifications, we would write reports in Spanish, Portuguese and English with suggestions on how the clients should improve their webpages. I was also in contact with the clients in meetings and worked remotely from my house for several months in 2020. I was very glad to be able to work with huge clients such as BBVA, Lush, Dollar General Cayuse, Banco Itaú, Lojas Americanas, Azul airlines, and many others. In this company, I received training and learned much about HTML, Accessibility, and Agile methodologies like SCRUM.

Mozio Group Database Administrator April 2019 - January 2020 (10 months)

Córdoba Province, Argentina

Mozio was my first experience in working with a system like ZenDesk where I managed data and contacted clients in three different languages Portuguese, Spanish, and English. I also Conducted presentations and group meetings in English and worked remotely from my house as well as in a co-working space. I learned a lot about foreign client management and etiquette and also had my first look at front and backend tied together to a product such as Mozio.

Education

UTN - Facultad Regional Cordoba

Diplomatura en Nuevas Tecnologias · (2020 - 2021)

Alura Cursos Online
Javascript - Vanilla JS · (2020 - 2020)

Google Mobile Academy
HTML / CSS Certification · (2020 - 2020)

SAE Institute
Audio Engineer, Sound Engineering · (2012 - 2013)